

# CONTACTS



Kharkiv, Ukraine



+38(099)401-62-15



denis\_pavlenko



denispavlenko94aqmail.com



denis-pavlenko



03.04.1994

#### SKILLS SUMMARY

HTML&CSS(SaSS/SCSS)



Crossbrowser and responsive layout



jQuery / JavaScript





Figma/Photoshop/Avocado/Zeplin

# **LANGUAGES**

Russian Native Ukraine Native

English Pre-Intermediate

#### **PROFILE**

I am a beginner Markup Developer with the knowledge required to the technical sphere of this direction. I already have some experience with functional.

I want to take part in a team of professionals to develop my skills and knowledge.

I am self-motivated, easy going and open to new concepts and responsibilities.

#### **PROJECTS**

#### <u>SpiderShiba</u>



(GitHub

# <u>Artificial-Int</u>



GitHub

# <u>Medical Center</u>







(**G**itHub @\_\_\_\_

#### Best Hotels



( GitHub



GitHub 👰

# <u>Football Apparel</u>



) <u>GitHub</u> 👰

# <u>Cosmetology</u> ) <u>GitHub</u>



#### WORK EXPERIENCE

# **Account & Project** Manager

at IconPartners July 2020 - till now

**Account Manager** 

Dec 2019 - June 2020

- Organizing and participating in negotiations with clients
- Preparing technical specifications/statements of work for the team
- Conducting weekly analyses of the legal team's reports
- Implementing quality control of the services provided

# at IT Svit

- · Handling incoming applications and calls • Customer support at every stage of sales
- Lead generation

# **Lead administrator** • Selling services and courses at Hillel IT School

Sept 2017 - Dec 2019

- Budget planning and expense reporting
- Setting up programs on computers

# Administrator. leather goods store

Oct 2014 - Sept 2017

- · Processing of incoming applications, selling
- Filling site content
- · Preparation and execution of documents for shipment

# **EDUCATION HISTORY**

2014 - 2019

# National Technical University "Kharkiv Polytechnic Institute"

Applied Mechanics, Master's degree

**Kharkiv Mechanical Engineering College Applied Mechanics** 

2014 - 2015

Kharkiv Mechanical Engineering College Economist, technician with a plan

#### ADDITIONAL EDUCATION

Hillel IT Shool

Course: "Front-end Basic: HTML&CSS"

• Hillel IT Shool

Course: "Front-end Pro: JavaScript" (now in the process of studying)

- Big Bang! English space | Course: "English"
- Foreign Language Studio "NewTone" | "English"